[
    {
      "id": 1,
      "question_type": "Matching Task",
      "question": "Tap all the letters that are the same as b.",
      "options": ["b", "d", "p", "q"],
      "answer": "b"
    },
    {
      "id": 2,
      "question_type": "Same/Different Task",
      "question": "Are these letters the same or different?",
      "options": ["b", "d"],
      "answer": "different"
    },
    {
      "id": 3,
      "question_type": "Matching Task",
      "question": "Tap all the letters that are the same as d.",
      "options": ["b", "d", "p", "q"],
      "answer": "d"
    },
    {
      "id": 4,
      "question_type": "Same/Different Task",
      "question": "Are these letters the same or different?",
      "options": ["p", "q"],
      "answer": "same"
    },
    {
      "id": 5,
      "question_type": "Matching Task",
      "question": "Tap all the letters that are the same as p.",
      "options": ["b", "d", "p", "q"],
      "answer": "p"
    },
    {
      "id": 6,
      "question_type": "Same/Different Task",
      "question": "Are these letters the same or different?",
      "options": ["b", "q"],
      "answer": "different"
    },
    {
      "id": 7,
      "question_type": "Matching Task",
      "question": "Tap all the letters that are the same as q.",
      "options": ["b", "d", "p", "q"],
      "answer": "q"
    },
    {
      "id": 8,
      "question_type": "Same/Different Task",
      "question": "Are these letters the same or different?",
      "options": ["p", "d"],
      "answer": "different"
    },
    {
      "id": 9,
      "question_type": "Matching Task",
      "question": "Tap all the letters that are the same as m.",
      "options": ["m", "n", "p", "q"],
      "answer": "m"
    },
    {
      "id": 10,
      "question_type": "Same/Different Task",
      "question": "Are these letters the same or different?",
      "options": ["m", "n"],
      "answer": "different"
    },
    {
      "id": 11,
      "question_type": "Matching Task",
      "question": "Tap all the letters that are the same as n.",
      "options": ["m", "n", "p", "q"],
      "answer": "n"
    },
    {
      "id": 12,
      "question_type": "Same/Different Task",
      "question": "Are these letters the same or different?",
      "options": ["m", "p"],
      "answer": "different"
    },
    {
      "id": 13,
      "question_type": "Matching Task",
      "question": "Tap all the letters that are the same as t.",
      "options": ["t", "f", "p", "q"],
      "answer": "t"
    },
    {
      "id": 14,
      "question_type": "Same/Different Task",
      "question": "Are these letters the same or different?",
      "options": ["t", "f"],
      "answer": "different"
    },
    {
      "id": 15,
      "question_type": "Matching Task",
      "question": "Tap all the letters that are the same as f.",
      "options": ["t", "f", "p", "q"],
      "answer": "f"
    },
    {
      "id": 16,
      "question_type": "Same/Different Task",
      "question": "Are these letters the same or different?",
      "options": ["t", "p"],
      "answer": "different"
    },
    {
      "id": 17,
      "question_type": "Matching Task",
      "question": "Tap all the letters that are the same as c.",
      "options": ["c", "o", "p", "q"],
      "answer": "c"
    },
    {
      "id": 18,
      "question_type": "Same/Different Task",
      "question": "Are these letters the same or different?",
      "options": ["c", "o"],
      "answer": "different"
    },
    {
      "id": 19,
      "question_type": "Matching Task",
      "question": "Tap all the letters that are the same as o.",
      "options": ["c", "o", "p", "q"],
      "answer": "o"
    },
    {
      "id": 20,
      "question_type": "Same/Different Task",
      "question": "Are these letters the same or different?",
      "options": ["o", "p"],
      "answer": "different"
    },
    {
      "id": 21,
      "question_type": "Matching Task",
      "question": "Tap all the letters that are the same as h.",
      "options": ["h", "k", "p", "q"],
      "answer": "h"
    },
    {
      "id": 22,
      "question_type": "Same/Different Task",
      "question": "Are these letters the same or different?",
      "options": ["h", "k"],
      "answer": "same"
    },
    {
      "id": 23,
      "question_type": "Matching Task",
      "question": "Tap all the letters that are the same as k.",
      "options": ["h", "k", "p", "q"],
      "answer": "k"
    },
    {
      "id": 24,
      "question_type": "Same/Different Task",
      "question": "Are these letters the same or different?",
      "options": ["h", "p"],
      "answer": "different"
    },
    {
      "id": 25,
      "question_type": "Matching Task",
      "question": "Tap all the letters that are the same as v.",
      "options": ["v", "u", "w", "x"],
      "answer": "v"
    },
    {
      "id": 26,
      "question_type": "Same/Different Task",
      "question": "Are these letters the same or different?",
      "options": ["v", "u"],
      "answer": "different"
    },
    {
      "id": 27,
      "question_type": "Matching Task",
      "question": "Tap all the letters that are the same as u.",
      "options": ["v", "u", "w", "x"],
      "answer": "u"
    },
    {
      "id": 28,
      "question_type": "Same/Different Task",
      "question": "Are these letters the same or different?",
      "options": ["v", "w"],
      "answer": "different"
    },
    {
      "id": 29,
      "question_type": "Matching Task",
      "question": "Tap all the letters that are the same as w.",
      "options": ["v", "u", "w", "x"],
      "answer": "w"
    },
    {
      "id": 30,
      "question_type": "Same/Different Task",
      "question": "Are these letters the same or different?",
      "options": ["w", "x"],
      "answer": "same"
    },
    {
      "id": 31,
      "question_type": "Matching Task",
      "question": "Tap all the letters that are the same as x.",
      "options": ["v", "u", "w", "x"],
      "answer": "x"
    },
    {
      "id": 32,
      "question_type": "Same/Different Task",
      "question": "Are these letters the same or different?",
      "options": ["v", "x"],
      "answer": "different"
    },
    {
      "id": 33,
      "question_type": "Matching Task",
      "question": "Tap all the letters that are the same as z.",
      "options": ["z", "y", "x", "w"],
      "answer": "z"
    },
    {
      "id": 34,
      "question_type": "Same/Different Task",
      "question": "Are these letters the same or different?",
      "options": ["z", "y"],
      "answer": "different"
    },
    {
      "id": 35,
      "question_type": "Matching Task",
      "question": "Tap all the letters that are the same as y.",
      "options": ["z", "y", "x", "w"],
      "answer": "y"
    },
    {
      "id": 36,
      "question_type": "Same/Different Task",
      "question": "Are these letters the same or different?",
      "options": ["z", "x"],
      "answer": "different"
    },
    {
      "id": 37,
      "question_type": "Matching Task",
      "question": "Tap all the letters that are the same as j.",
      "options": ["j", "i", "l", "k"],
      "answer": "j"
    },
    {
      "id": 38,
      "question_type": "Same/Different Task",
      "question": "Are these letters the same or different?",
      "options": ["j", "i"],
      "answer": "different"
    },
    {
      "id": 39,
      "question_type": "Matching Task",
      "question": "Tap all the letters that are the same as i.",
      "options": ["j", "i", "l", "k"],
      "answer": "i"
    },
    {
      "id": 40,
      "question_type": "Same/Different Task",
      "question": "Are these letters the same or different?",
      "options": ["i", "l"],
      "answer": "different"
    },
    {
      "id": 41,
      "question_type": "Matching Task",
      "question": "Tap all the letters that are the same as l.",
      "options": ["j", "i", "l", "k"],
      "answer": "l"
    },
    {
      "id": 42,
      "question_type": "Same/Different Task",
      "question": "Are these letters the same or different?",
      "options": ["j", "k"],
      "answer": "different"
    },
    {
      "id": 43,
      "question_type": "Matching Task",
      "question": "Tap all the letters that are the same as k.",
      "options": ["j", "i", "l", "k"],
      "answer": "k"
    },
    {
      "id": 44,
      "question_type": "Same/Different Task",
      "question": "Are these letters the same or different?",
      "options": ["l", "k"],
      "answer": "same"
    },
    {
      "id": 45,
      "question_type": "Matching Task",
      "question": "Tap all the letters that are the same as a.",
      "options": ["a", "e", "i", "o"],
      "answer": "a"
    },
    {
      "id": 46,
      "question_type": "Same/Different Task",
      "question": "Are these letters the same or different?",
      "options": ["a", "e"],
      "answer": "different"
    },
    {
      "id": 47,
      "question_type": "Matching Task",
      "question": "Tap all the letters that are the same as e.",
      "options": ["a", "e", "i", "o"],
      "answer": "e"
    },
    {
      "id": 48,
      "question_type": "Same/Different Task",
      "question": "Are these letters the same or different?",
      "options": ["a", "i"],
      "answer": "different"
    },
    {
      "id": 49,
      "question_type": "Matching Task",
      "question": "Tap all the letters that are the same as i.",
      "options": ["a", "e", "i", "o"],
      "answer": "i"
    },
    {
      "id": 50,
      "question_type": "Same/Different Task",
      "question": "Are these letters the same or different?",
      "options": ["i", "o"],
      "answer": "different"
    },
    {
      "id": 51,
      "question_type": "Matching Task",
      "question": "Tap all the letters that are the same as o.",
      "options": ["a", "e", "i", "o"],
      "answer": "o"
    },
    {
      "id": 52,
      "question_type": "Same/Different Task",
      "question": "Are these letters the same or different?",
      "options": ["e", "o"],
      "answer": "different"
    },
    {
      "id": 53,
      "question_type": "Matching Task",
      "question": "Tap all the letters that are the same as u.",
      "options": ["u", "y", "o", "e"],
      "answer": "u"
    },
    {
      "id": 54,
      "question_type": "Same/Different Task",
      "question": "Are these letters the same or different?",
      "options": ["u", "y"],
      "answer": "different"
    },
    {
      "id": 55,
      "question_type": "Matching Task",
      "question": "Tap all the letters that are the same as y.",
      "options": ["u", "y", "o", "e"],
      "answer": "y"
    },
    {
      "id": 56,
      "question_type": "Same/Different Task",
      "question": "Are these letters the same or different?",
      "options": ["e", "y"],
      "answer": "different"
    },
    {
      "id": 57,
      "question_type": "Matching Task",
      "question": "Tap all the letters that are the same as z.",
      "options": ["z", "y", "x", "w"],
      "answer": "z"
    },
    {
      "id": 58,
      "question_type": "Same/Different Task",
      "question": "Are these letters the same or different?",
      "options": ["z", "y"],
      "answer": "different"
    },
    {
      "id": 59,
      "question_type": "Matching Task",
      "question": "Tap all the letters that are the same as v.",
      "options": ["v", "u", "w", "x"],
      "answer": "v"
    },
    {
      "id": 60,
      "question_type": "Same/Different Task",
      "question": "Are these letters the same or different?",
      "options": ["v", "x"],
      "answer": "different"
    },
    {
      "id": 61,
      "question_type": "Matching Task",
      "question": "Tap all the letters that are the same as v.",
      "options": ["v", "u", "w", "x"],
      "answer": "v"
    },
    {
      "id": 62,
      "question_type": "Same/Different Task",
      "question": "Are these letters the same or different?",
      "options": ["v", "u"],
      "answer": "different"
    },
    {
      "id": 63,
      "question_type": "Matching Task",
      "question": "Tap all the letters that are the same as j.",
      "options": ["j", "i", "l", "k"],
      "answer": "j"
    },
    {
      "id": 64,
      "question_type": "Same/Different Task",
      "question": "Are these letters the same or different?",
      "options": ["j", "k"],
      "answer": "same"
    }
  ]
  